getmoremomentum.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy - Get More Momentum

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**Privacy Policy for www.GetMoreMomentum.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@getmoremomentum.com.

At www.GetMoreMomentum.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.GetMoreMomentum.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.GetMoreMomentum.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.GetMoreMomentum.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.GetMoreMomentum.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.GetMoreMomentum.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.GetMoreMomentum.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.GetMoreMomentum.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.GetMoreMomentum.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;

(b) information about any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications; and

(d) OTHER INFORMATION.

**Information about website visits**

We may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability, and for marketing purposes.

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you.

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookie by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

**Using personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:

(a) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;

(b) send information (other than marketing communications) to you which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology;

(c) send to you marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by clicking ‘Unsubscribe’ at the bottom of any email you receive from us)

(d) OTHER USES.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

**Other disclosures**

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to countries including the United States, Japan, which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. You expressly agree to such transfers.

**Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

We do not store any of your credit card information. All credit card information you provide on our secure severs is passed directly to our secure 3rd party shopping cart which uses industry standard 128 bit secure sockets layer (SSL) technology to encrypt sensitive information such as your credit card and other financial information. This includes the credit card number, expiry date, and billing address.

**Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy be email.

**Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites.

**Contact**

You can contact us at [support[at]getmoremomentum.com](mailto:support@getmoremomentum.com)
